[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the literal meaning of the Japanese word hime which refers to a popular cut?", "correct_answer": "Princess", "incorrect_answers": ["Flower", "Tail", "Dragon"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A tropical storm with sustained winds exceeding 33 meters per second, which occurs in the Northwest Pacific Ocean west of the dateline, is called this.", "correct_answer": "Typhoon", "incorrect_answers": ["Severe tropical cyclone", "Hurricane", "Severe cyclonic storm"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which was the first TV series regularly broadcast in color?", "correct_answer": "Bonanza", "incorrect_answers": ["Gunsmoke", "The Flintstones", "Hawaii 5-0"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Mobster and monster, Cody Jarrett, went out in a blaze of glory, literally. In what movie does Cody Jarrett declare Made it, Ma, top of the world! just before the gas tank he is sitting on explodes?", "correct_answer": "White Heat", "incorrect_answers": ["Casablanca", "Public Enemy", "The Third Man"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the motion picture, Goldfinger, the antagonist relies on this gas for accomplishing his goals.", "correct_answer": "Delta 9", "incorrect_answers": ["Beta 7", "Alpha 5", "Kappa 2"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The zebrafish (Girella zebra), which can be recognised by its pale body and yellow fins, is endemic to which region?", "correct_answer": "Australian waters", "incorrect_answers": ["Amazon River Basin", "The Caribbean", "Japan waters"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "According to GlobalNet UK, less than what percentage of 500 Chinese cities surveyed have clean air?", "correct_answer": "1%", "incorrect_answers": ["15%", "24%", "30%"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The flip book was an early attempt at animation. It was a book of stills that, when flipped, showed motion. When was this book first patented?", "correct_answer": "1868", "incorrect_answers": ["1834", "1899", "1789"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does killer Jame Gumb do with the skins taken from his victims in the 1991 movie The Silence of the Lambs?", "correct_answer": "He intends to make a suit out of them.", "incorrect_answers": ["He keeps them as trophies on his walls.", "He makes furniture from them.", "He eats them."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What name is used to refer to the scorpion species also known as Omdurman scorpion, and Israeli desert scorpion?", "correct_answer": "Deathstalker", "incorrect_answers": ["Bonebreaker", "Windchaser", "Nightkiller"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following states of America is an inland one and has an official motto that does not come from Latin?", "correct_answer": "Montana", "incorrect_answers": ["Virginia", "Oklahoma", "South Carolina"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these names is commonly used for the carrion flies, belonging to the family Calliphoridae?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Greenbottle", "Blow-flies", "Cluster flies"]}]